easymusicdownload.com 2019-01-20

# None

The site is committed to protecting your privacy. 

We provide this notice to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way information is collected and used. We will only use the information we collect for the purposes of providing you with a more personalized and useful membership experience. At no time will we sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties. 

Registration  
By registering with the site, you can take advantage of our unique, personalized features and services. Upon registering, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail address, a unique password, zip or postal code. This information is collected for personal identification and also allows you access to your own account and various features.

Contests  
When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, phone number, or e-mail address so that we can administer the contest and notify winners. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

Online Surveys  
We value opinions and comments from members, and you may have the opportunity to give us your feedback through online surveys. In conducting these surveys, we may ask for your name, address, or e-mail address so that we can appropriately identify you. Survey information collected will be aggregated and used to make improvements to the site. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

Links  
This Web site contains links to other partner sites. Please be aware that this site is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Cookies  
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by our browser on your computer's hard drive. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to recognize you. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The only personal information a cookie contains is the information you provide yourself. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can set your browser to block them in the future. 

IP Addresses  
This site collects the IP addresses used to access our service and the dates and times of access. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track the user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Notification  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post notice of a privacy policy update on our Web site so that our members may view our updated policy on an ongoing basis and be aware of what information we collect.
